gameguru.in 2011-08-24

# Privacy | Game Guru - GameGuru.in

The terms ‘Gameguru.in’ and ‘www.Gameguru.in’ are used in this document (or Agreement) to refer to the Web site itself.

Privacy issues are a high priority for us at www.GameGuru.in and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

GameGuru.in does not spam or sell/lease its user information to third parties.

Policy Coverage

This Privacy Policy covers GameGuru.in’s treatment of personally identifiable information that GameGuru.in collects when you are on the www.GameGuru.in site, and when you use GameGuru.in’s services. This policy also covers GameGuru.in’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that GameGuru.in’s business partners share with GameGuru.in. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that GameGuru.in does not own or control, or to people that GameGuru.in does not employ or manage.

Personal Information Collected by GameGuru.in

ONLINE REGISTRATION: In order to become a GameGuru.in member, you must first create a member account on GameGuru.in by providing information about yourself including but not limited to name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, birth date, a brief summary of yourself and a password. GameGuru.in checks for the validity of the email addresses.

OPTIONAL PROFILE INFORMATION: Once your provide the basic information to create an account, you will have the opportunity to provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, interests, professional and academic background and favorites. Provision of this additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional; it allows you to better identify yourself and create superior networking opportunities with others through shared contexts. but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities on GameGuru.in. Your Profile information can only be viewed by other GameGuru.in visitors or registered members or members of your personal network only depending on the option you choose.

RECOGNIZING YOU AS A GameGuru.in MEMBER: For GameGuru.in to recognize you as a registered member, you must login with your login email and password. At the time of login, you will have the option to instruct the site to remember you so when you come back the next time to use GameGuru.in, you would not have to login with your email and password. As is common in the industry, GameGuru.in uses the technology of cookies and site log files to monitor user registration, to recognize registered members when they revisit the site and to track site usage. Our ability to identify you as a registered member allows us to customize the GameGuru.in experience and to protect your personal information based on your account settings.

INTERNET COMMUNICATION PROTOCOL INFORMATION: The communication standards of the Internet industry transmit the URL of the site from which you visit www.GameGuru.in, the IP address of your computer, the IP address of your ISP, various attributes of your computer such as operating system, resolution and browser software, and the date and time of your various requests for pages on www.GameGuru.in. GameGuru.in file logging system automatically logs all of this information in its log files for its analysis.

NEWSLETTER SUBSCRIPTIONS: Visitors to GameGuru.in may also sign up with their name and email address for a variety of newsletters that GameGuru.in produces with varying frequency (e.g., News headlines) without having to register. GameGuru.in confirms the subscription by sending an email to the email address specified before sending the newsletter.

Use of Information by GameGuru.in

GameGuru.in is an online website that offers a variety of services designed to connect people from around the world. The information, whether personal information of any form of self-expression is used to help you describe yourself to other users. GameGuru.in also collects additional information in order to operate and improve our service. www.GameGuru.in is the sole owner of the information collected on the GameGuru.in site.

VISIBILITY OF PUBLIC CREATIVE CONTRIBUTIONS: In addition to being a social and professional networking site, GameGuru.in also provides a variety of forums for its members to express themselves in the form of articles, columns, opinions, comments, reviews, art and photographs. Since this expression is linked to the member’s identity and the expression is in the public domain, the compilation of a member’s creative contributions to GameGuru.in will be visible to all visitors of GameGuru.in whether or not they are registered members of GameGuru.in.

VISIBILITY OF PRIVATE MESSAGES WITHIN NETWORK: You will be able to create and share messages within your personal network. The visibility of these private notes will be restricted to your network unless you or one of the members in your network choose to forward it to others within or outside www.GameGuru.in.

SHARING OF INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES: GameGuru.in takes your privacy very seriously. GameGuru.in will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties unless it is to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. As an example, we send your information to a credit card processing company to process a payment you have made for the use of a GameGuru.in service. These third parties are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. In addition, GameGuru.in may share your information to send direct mailers or complimentary coupons/offers to a mailing agency to process postal mailing. Again, such an agency would be bound by strict confidentiality agreements that limit their use of such information.

EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS: GameGuru.in generally communicates with you as a registered member of GameGuru.in through the primary email that you have specified at the time of registration. This is also used as the login text string in conjunction with the password to authenticate you on the www.GameGuru.in site. Your email and password are never shared with anybody within or outside GameGuru.in. GameGuru.in uses this email address to send you three types of communications:

Sending you emails related to the proper functioning of your account (e.g. when you receive a response to a classified you have posted on GameGuru.in or when you receive an invitation to join the personal network of another person). Sending you newsletters that you have subscribed to. Sending you occasional announcements about changes in GameGuru.in’s policies or promotions introduction of new services  
Please note that these email communications may contain commercial messages of advertisers; however, GameGuru.in does not provide your personal information or emails to any of the advertisers; we just include the advertising banners they provide us in the emails that we send. As always you can opt out of the newsletters or promotional announcements.

PARTNERING WITH OTHERS: GameGuru.in may partner with other online services to offer a combined service. Whenever we offer such combined services, GameGuru.in will make it clear who the partner is and it will be entirely up to you to use or not to use the service. Where any personal information is passed along to the partner you will be informed prior to that sharing.

PROVISION OF AGGREGATE DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES: GameGuru.in reserves the right to provide aggregate demographic information of its member base to advertisers and others so as to attract pertinent advertisers to advertise on GameGuru.in. We do not shared personal information of individual users with advertisers.

COMMUNICATIONS TO OTHERS FROM YOU THROUGH GameGuru.in: You will be able to send emails to others — members and non-members — through the GameGuru.in system. For example, you may send a comment on an article written by another member. Or you may send an email invitation to a non-member to join your personal network. In these instances, these emails will list your name and email address in the header of the message. The recipients of these emails initiated by you will get to know your name and email address. GameGuru.in is not responsible for how these recipients use this information. Your contact information will only be shared with another member only if both of you indicated you would like to establish contact with each other.

COMMUNICATIONS FROM OTHERS TO YOU THROUGH GameGuru.in: Only registered members of GameGuru.in are allowed to communicate with you through GameGuru.in through a form on GameGuru.in. Unless and until you respond to this email, they will not get to know your email address. You may, however, choose an account setting that prevents any other member from contacting you or inviting you to join their personal network.

DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW: It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
